https://www.adirondackenvironmental.com/privacy-policy

Test My WaterAnalytical TestingIndustrial HygieneMaterial & Product TestingField ServicesWater Quality MonitoringSoil & Sludge SamplingIndustrial Hygiene SamplingWaste Stream SamplingAir AnalysisWhy AdirondackSuperior MethodologyCutting-Edge TechnologyQuality Assurance Program
Experience is the Solution
O: 518-434-4546 F: 518-434-0891
Test My WaterAnalytical TestingIndustrial HygieneMaterial & Product TestingField ServicesAir AnalysisWhy Adirondack
HomePrivacy PolicyYou are here HomePrivacy Policy
Contact Us With any questions!
Privacy Policy
This is the web site of: Adirondack Environmental Services, Inc, 314 N. Pearl Street, Albany, NY USA 12207Phone:  800-848-0983Fax: 518-434-0891E-Mail: info@adirondackenvironmental.comFor each visitor to our Website, our Web server automatically recognizes only the user's domain name, not the e-mail address. We collect only the domain name, but not the e-mail address of visitors to our Web page. We collect: The e-mail addresses of those who communicate with us via e-mail Aggregate information on what pages users access or visit User-specific information on what pages users access or visit Information volunteered by the user, such as survey information and/or site registrations.The information we collect is used: To improve the content of our Web page To notify users about updates to our Web site Share with agents or contractors who assist us in providing support for our internal operations To contact users for our own company's marketing communications or customer support purposesWe do not share this information with other organizations, unless: It is legally required that we do so at the request of governmental authorities conducting an investigation It is legally required that we do so to verify or enforce compliance with the policies governing our Website and applicable laws or to protect against misuse or unauthorized use of our Website It is to a successor entity in connection with a corporate merger, consolidation, sale of assets or other corporate change respecting the WebsiteCookies: We use cookies to store visitors' preferences, record session information, or record information on what pages users access or visit.Email Opt-in/Opt-Out Procedures: If you supply us with your email address, you may receive periodic mailings from us with information on new products and services or upcoming events. If you do not wish to receive such mailings, please let us know by sending an email with the Subject Line "UNSUBSCRIBE" to info@adirondackenvironmental.com.Mailing Information: If you supply us with your postal address on-line you may receive periodic mailings from us with information on new products and services or upcoming events. If you do not wish to receive such mailings, please email us at info@adirondackenvironmental.com with your name, company, exact name and address and phone number.Telephone Information: If you supply us with your telephone number you may receive telephone contact from us with information regarding new products and services or upcoming events. If you do not wish to receive such telephone calls, please let us know by sending us e-mailing info@adirondackenvironmental.com.Ad Servers: We do not partner with or have special relationships with any ad server companies.Other:1 From time to time, we may use user-provided information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will contact you before we use your data for these new purposes to notify you of the policy change and to provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses.2. Upon request we provide site visitors with access to all information [including proprietary information] that we maintain about them. Users can access this information by e-mail us at the above address.3. Upon request we offer visitors the ability to have inaccuracies corrected in contact information, communications that the consumer/visitor has directed to the site. Consumers can have this information corrected by sending us e-mail at the above address.4. Security. We have appropriate security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our site.If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, you may contact us at the above addresses or phone number, The DMA's Committee on Ethical Business Practices at mgoldberger@the-dma.org state or local chapters of the Better Business Bureau, state or local consumer protection office, The Federal Trade Commission by phone at 202.FTC-HELP (202.382.4357. fax 202.382.4357) or electronically at http://www.ftc.gov/ftc/complaint.htm.
Contact
314 N. Pearl Street, Albany, NY 12207
+1 (518) 434-4546
+1 (800) 848-4983
+1 (518) 434-0891
Resources
Forms Contact Resource Center Privacy Policy Site Map Feedback
© 2020 Adirondack Environmental Services, Inc. All Rights Reserved.
Website By: Web Instinct
Top
